aapc.com 2019-11-20

# Privacy Statement - AAPC

#### Information Collected 

AAPC gathers two types of information about users: 

  * Information provided through optional, voluntary submissions. These include, but are not limited to, applying for membership, purchasing products or services, participating in surveys, submitting questions or comments, or requesting information. 
  * Information gathered through aggregated visitor tracking derived mainly by tallying page views throughout its websites. This information allows them to better tailor its services to its members and prospective members. 

#### Information Usage 

AAPC uses the contact information you provide to help create and continually improve its services for you. It uses payment information for payment processing purposes and takes steps to secure that information (noted in the security section below). It creates and maintains other information such as customer or member account status, choice of services, and customer or member logs in the normal course of providing service. AAPC uses your information to make your experience with its services more personalized, convenient and relevant to you. 

AAPC uses your information to communicate with you via letter, email or phone concerning the status of your account, billing issues, and service updates. Periodically it will also send you company and industry newsletters, product updates, and promotions from its select partners because we believe this information may be valuable to you. If you wish to not receive these types of correspondence, you may opt-out, or unsubscribe by contacting us at 801-236-2200 or e-mailing [optoutpn@aapc.com](mailto:optoutpn@aapc.com). Customers may not opt-out of receiving information from AAPC that is essential for maintaining or updating customers account or system information. 

#### Information Security 

AAPC has security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information. It restricts access to member information by AAPC's business partners who may need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve its services. These parties are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

AAPC treats your personal information in a confidential manner. Its employees and other authorized personnel are required to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. It restricts access to personal information about you to only those individuals who have a business reason to know the information, such as in order to provide services for you. It also maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect such information. All employees and other authorized personnel are required to comply with its established policies, including this Privacy Policy. 

#### How You Can Access and Change Information

If you are a registered member of the AAPC website, you may review and update/correct your personal information on the Profile/Preferences webpage or by contacting AAPC at (801) 236-2200. 

#### Information Sharing 

AAPC may share some information with select partners providing services that may be of interest to its members and prospective members. The information is shared on a very limited basis and available only with a non-disclosure agreement and single use restriction. Such third parties do not have the right to use your information for any purpose other than to inform of the applicable service. 

AAPC will not otherwise disclose personal or account information unless there is reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of AAPC, its customers, or others. It may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable laws or where AAPC has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. 

AAPC also will not disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that AAPC stores or transmits for its customers except where: (a) it is a matter or public safety or policy; (b) it is in connection with the transfer of other business assets; (c) it is required to cooperate with orders, warrants, or other legal process that AAPC determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and (d) it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by AAPC and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime. 

If AAPC sells, assigns or transfers the part of its business that provides a particular service to you, your personally identifiable information may be sold, assigned or transferred as apart of such transaction. 

#### Your Consent 

By using this site, becoming an AAPC member, purchasing products or services from them, or engaging AAPC in any way, you consent to the collection and use of information collected as noted in this privacy statement. If AAPC decides to change its privacy policy, it will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information it collects, how it uses the information, and under what circumstances AAPC discloses it. 

American Academy Holdings LLC  
2233 S Presidents Dr., Suite F  
Salt Lake City, UT 84120
